that's going to come to work each and
every day, compete, play at a high
level, and going to give it his all
every single down, you know, and not
only, you know, play for myself, man,
but play for my, you know, my, you know,
my teammates, you know, uh, you know,
try to chase perfection each and every
day, not only for myself, but, you know,
also this young this young secondary,
you know, I'm just ready to put it put
it all on tape, man. You know, know uh
just let my action speak.
>> Nikki,
>> um, hi EC. Um, just your your play
style. You play very tough the way you
hit. Have you always been like that
where you have no problem just going in
and flattening somebody?
>> Always been that way since since since
pop one or since I was since I was
young. Uh, you know, uh, didn't know I
was going to be this small, you know,
growing up. Thought I was going to be a
little taller, but uh, you know, uh,
wasn't, you know, like I said, the
statue of the body wasn't always, you
know, big. So, what I did was I just I
just played bigger. you know, uh, I
tried to be different in different ways
far as, you know, like I said, my play
style playing bigger and most
importantly, not only get, you know, PBU
was coming out of coming coming out of
college, I wanted to get picks, you
know, cuz Pix is what get you noticed,
man. The ball, you know, the game is
about the ball. So, uh, dropped a lot
last year. Dropped a lot last year, but,
you know, we going we going to make sure
we get those this this year, you know,
in order to help our, you know, help
this team.
>> Has your height ever been a hindrance to
you or you've always been able to just
overcome it and play bigger?
>> Yeah, always. always since you know like
I said since since I was young you know
I always never used I never used it as
an excuse you know uh because you know
by me being this small you know I got
you know other things that you know I
got advantage you know my quickness and
my feet you know uh you know always you
know low to the ground you know so uh I
just you know kind of kind of use my use
my advantages with it
>> yeah K back to you
>> hey had one more question too you talk
about playing like that Tasmanian devil
where do you get that from where does
that stem from?
>> Well, I think you
>> I think I think it's just a passion,
man. It's just a, you know, the passion
of love in the game of football, you
know. Uh, like I said, when I'm out
there, man, you know, I maybe they call
it sharp man syndrome. I don't I don't
know, you know. But when I'm out there,
you know, I try to play like I'm the
biggest human being, you know, but you
know, even though even though I'm the
smallest, but I just feel like, you
know, I'm the biggest and the baddest,
you know what, out there. So, uh, that's
what I mean by having that, you know,
that just being that Tasmanian devil and
energy like that, you know, it's it's
contagious, man. You know, when when
guys see that, you know, it's another
guy out there playing with passion and
and energy, you know, you it kind of
becomes contagious, and that's what kind
of guy I am. You know, that's what I
feel like I bring to the table.
>> Thank you.
>> Apologize if this was asked already. I
got on late. But, uh, first of all,
welcome to Washington. You're very
versatile inside, outside. Do you have a
preference and and has Washington kind
of told you what they see in you in
terms of how they want to play you on
this defense?
>> Uh, I just look at myself as a as a
hybrid, man. You know, when they ask me,
hey, you know, what are you, man? I'm a
hybrid. I could play corner, I could
play nickel, uh, safety, you know,
whatever, whatever the team need me to
do. Uh, you know, that's what that's
that's what I'll do. You know, I like I
say, I've been in the league, you know,
quite quite some time. you know, I've
been through different schemes,
different defenses. So, you know, I had,
you know, I've I've saw, you know, I've
saw it all. So, uh, when they ask me,
you know, far as my position, you know,
I could play anything. Anything that the
team needs me to do, you know, I I'll
figure it out. You know, I put myself in
a position to make to make plays and
make the defense better.
>> And, you know, obviously dating back to
that playoff game and, you know, you you
probably obviously have a all too
familiar remembrance of that because you
I think you broke your arm that game
against Commanders.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, obviously going up against Jaden
Daniels, game planning for Jaden
Daniels, now you have him as your
teammate. Uh, what is that what is that
like now?
>> Uh, it's it's it's fun, man. You know,
uh, I know it's going to be fun. Uh,
Jaden, you know, easily one of the best
quarterbacks in in the league and and
he's young, you know, you know,
ceillingness to the roof, you know. So,
uh, um, it's going to be exciting, man.
Just competing with those guys every
day, you know. Terry, you know, uh just
can't wait, you know, for those matchups
at practice going against him. You know,
he's an unbelievable wide receiver. Been
doing it a long time in this league. So,
uh just learning even learning learning
from him, you know, uh what he look for
in other DBs, how can I get better with
this and you know, also helping him as
well and also helping these young
younger guys. So, uh I know it's going
to be fun, man. It's going to be
exciting, man. I'm just, you know, I'm
just glad to be a part of it.
>> Liam,
>> hi. Welcome to Washington. You mentioned
that you've seen a lot of different
schemes throughout your career. I'm
curious, what did they tell you to
expect from uh this Donte Jones scheme
in its first season?
>> Um,
just expect to make plays on the ball,
man. You know, that's that's a that's
about it, you know. Uh, like I say, he's
a smart guy. You know, he's he's going
to put players put us in a good
position, you know, to make plays. So
that's that's you know that's that's all
I think you know that that he's going to
bring to the table for as you know you
know the defense like I say like I said
before he's very smart you know he's
been playing football a long time. So uh
I I know he's going to put you know the
the defense a lot of situations you know
know to be able to make plays on the
ball and get the ball back to the
offense.
>> Thank you
>> Donna.
>> Hello. Hi. Welcome to Washington.
>> How you doing? Um, when you look at this
team as a whole and coming to
Washington, why does this team fits you
so well?
>> Um,
you know, I think it was God's plan,
man. You know, uh, like, you know, I had
a former former, you know, uh, close
brother that I knew, you know, he, you
know, he passed away and, uh, he, you
know, he talked about the Washington
Commanders, you know, he wanted to be
here. His mom wanted wanted him to be
here and, you know, it just go full
circle. He always talked about Jaden D.
he always talked about playing with but
playing with Jaden. Um and you know I
you know I'm you know I'm familiar with
a lot of guys you know on the defensive
side. Butler uh with Percy um um Mikey
you know so just being able to play with
those guys man you know I I just know
it's going to be exciting you know and I
I definitely like those colors too man.
Like those colors.
>> You ready to sport those? So, who since
you know Mikey and Percy and you know
yourself, who's the biggest trash talker
between you three?
>> Me. Easy. Easily. Easily me. It's It's
no question about it. But, you know, it
it comes from a good place though. You
know, like I said, I'm a highly
competitive guy. Like highly
competitive. You know, I I never say
crazy things, you know, personal things.
It just I'm a highly competitive guy.
when I'm going against a a person across
me, I just want your best in, you know,
I want I want your best cuz, you know,
I'm trying to give you my uh best. So,
uh easily out of all us, you know,
Mikey, he don't really talk. Mikey is
the kind of guy, you know, he let his
game speak. So, um you know, but he's
definitely a pit bull, too, but you
know, on the on the other side, he's you
know, he's more of a he's not really a
talkative guy. I I you know, I would say
I do the most talking.
>> Thanks. Welcome.
>> Thank you,
>> David.
Hey Emmy, congratulations and welcome.
Um, kind of going back to that trash
talking, actually, one of the more
popular stories that has been
circulating around the commander circle
since uh, you guys agreed to this deal
is your trash talking to Justin
Jefferson and having that game where you
kind of just shut him down. And I know
he talked to the media in Minnesota
about that interaction uh, glowingly
about you as a competitor. You're going
to see him again this season. What is
what does that kind of showcase about
you and your competitiveness and to have
the respect of Justin? I know you guys
have a history as well. How what does
that mean for you as a professional?
>> I mean, it's it's, you know, it's it's I
mean, it's cool. You know, me and him
have a mutual respect. You know, like I
said, we've been we all know we've been
going to each other since we was young,
you know, since we was high school,
college, you know, so I respect his
game, you know, at a high level. I'm
pretty sure, you know, he respect my
game. We've had those talks about, you
know, just just the respect we have for
each other's each other's game. But at
the end of the day, man, he's arguably
the best receiver in the league, you
know, so uh one of one of the best
receivers in the league. So it's like
why not you know uh you want to go
against the best to you know in order to
put your name on a category or you know
to sharpen your knife you know each and
every time you go out there you have to
go against the best and just to pick it
back on you know Terry you know uh one
of the best in the league you know when
when healthy. So it's like going against
him every day at practice you know
that's going to sharpen my knife and I'm
pretty sure you know him going against
me is going to sharpen his. So, uh, you
know, it's it's it's it's always a, you
know, a competitive, but it's it always
come from a good side. You know, I'm
never, like I said before, I'm never
going to say anything personal. It just,
you know, I love the game of ball, man.
You know, I, you know, I always try to
try to find anything to get better.
>> Absolutely. And, uh, speaking from a
competitor, Donte Jones, coming from the
Minnesota Vikings coaching staff here to
Washington, you have to believe that he
saw something in you, those meetings
between the Vikings and the Lions that
made him want to bring you over. So, how
much does that kind of that that
compliment through action mean for you?
>> Uh, it's it's always good, you know,
when you got a coach, you know, that's
in your corner and and believe in your
your ability, you know, uh, you know,
that that tells you about the different
mindset that that you have, you know.
Uh, it just it just also builds the even
more confidence that you already have in
yourself, you know. So, you know, I got
a fresh start here. I just can't wait
to, like I said, man, put it on tape,
man. you know, show show this, you know,
earn respect from my teammates, from my
coaches, you know, because, you know,
it's respect is never never never given,
man. It's earned, you know. So, I just
want to do that. Uh, and like I said,
not only, you know, help myself, but
help my teammates.
>> Thank you,
>> Ben.
>> Hi. Uh, welcome uh to town. My
colleagues have asked most of the
questions I was going to ask, but um in
terms of the new defense, the new
defensive coordinator came from
Minnesota under Brian Flores. If we
presume to some degree that that's kind
of the scheme, a very aggressive scheme
that seems like it would fit your
mentality. How do you kind of you ever
look at that and think, boy, if I was
going to be on that defense, I would be
doing this and that.
>> Um we I watched a little bit of it when
I was at, you know, I saw it, you know,
a little bit of it when I was at the at
the lines. You know, I always said, you
know, I couldn't wait, you know, I would
like to play that kind of style of
defense. And it's crazy how, you know,
that those words took a full circle, you
know, and now that I'm I'm on that on
that defense that he run, I I just know
moral of the story, man. It's going to
be exciting, man. It's going to be fun,
you know, uh, and we going to get after
the ball. We going to get after the
quarterback, you know, cuz, you know,
like I say, the game is, you know, the
game is about the ball, man. And he's
going to do whatever he can to put us in
the position to get it. you know, I'm
talking about from every level, the the
D line, the linebackers, the backing,
you know, uh, and he got the right guys
to do it.
>> And just in terms of your off seasonason
and kind of what you go do from here
before camp and all that stuff, what do
you kind of do? What's your training
like?
>> That's a good question. Most
importantly, man, all those drop picks I
had last year. I'm most definitely been
on the jug machines for sure. You know,
we can't drop those. We can't miss miss
out on those opportunities. But uh to
pick it back off you say uh just you
know just focusing on my body man you
know of course um getting you know
keeping getting my feet back under me uh
you know strengthening myself
conditioning you know just working like
a pro man you know uh always you know
putting getting maintenance on my on my
body you know just making sure you know
when I come in you know I'm I'm you know
I'm healthy you know I was at like I
said I was at the Lions two two seasons
you know played a a full season healthy
you know so uh just just continue doing
that you know um staying staying and
available.
>> Blake,
welcome to DC. And uh you know, you come
from the Detroit and and uh Coach
Campbell there, you know, everyone talks
about the culture there. Well, in
Washington, everyone talks about the
culture that Coach Quinn has put in. Is
that something that you, you know, uh
impressed you and made you want to come
to Washington?
>> Definitely. Definitely. Uh they they
definitely have similar, like, you know,
they definitely has similarities. both
both are hell of a leaders. Um love the
game of football. Um you know uh and and
their players coaches, you know, they
they they know about the players. They
know what the players go through, you
know. So, and they do they have the best
interest into the players, you know. So,
just talking to him, you know, we had a
great great conversation over the phone,
you know. Uh I just I just can't wait to
get started, you know. I just can't wait
to get started, man. And and like I
said, like like the words that they say
in Detroit, man, I can't wait to run
through a wall for him. And it's so
crazy how the names are so similar. Dan
Quinn and Dan is is just crazy. But, you
know, I I just can't can't wait to
showcase, you know, um what I can do,
you know, for him, you know, and this
and this, uh team.
>> And then a couple years ago, you know,
there was a video that went viral with
you in the locker room in Detroit and
you were talking about how you came from
the mud, you know, came from the dirt to
see where you are right now. You know,
what would you say to everyone out there
that you know that's been up against the
odds? Um, you know, uh, always believe
in yourself, man. You know, always
believe in yourself, you know. Never let
no one tell you what you can't do, you
know. Uh, if they tell you you can't,
then they tripping, you know. Uh, always
go for what you believe in, man. You
know, cuz soon those same daughters,
they're going to become believers, you
know, when they see, you know, when they
see you do your thing. So, always be
confident in in yourself, man. You know,
uh only the only only person you should
fear is God, you know, cuz he's the only
person that can move mountains, you
know. So, uh, that's the word that I
give, you know, I give to to to my
younger fellas.
>> All right. Congrats.
>> Appreciate it.
>> All right. Thanks everybody. Appreciate
it. Thank you.